Viewers all over the world, we have been on journey of salvation
I know you have been listening to the message 'the beauty of life'.
The beauty of life does not depend on how happy we are,
but on how happy others can be because of us.
How many people are happy because of you?
How many lives have you touched today?
Don't forget somebody needs something you possess.
It may be your love, it may be your smile with all your heart.
It may be your money.
You may say you are poor.
You may be surprised to see someone who is poorer than you are.
This means, someone is in need of us.
No matter how little, how small - someone is in need of us.
If you cannot part with little, you will not be able to part with much.
Viewers, the journey of salvation.
I break all self-will within your heart - be broken in the name of Jesus!
Every self-will within your heart, be broken in the name of Jesus!
What you want to do is not what you are doing.
Every self-will be broken in the name of Jesus.
Let the will of God be done!
Viewers, begin to confess those self-wills, fleshly desires,
those things that come to tempt you, those things you try to resist.
What you want to do is not what you find yourself doing.
If that, it is the sin in your life.
Be broken in the name of Jesus!
Be disconnected!
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Salvation - ready to be delivered.
I can see you being delivered in the name of Jesus!
Self-thought, self-will within your heart.
Faith is of man's heart.
For the Word of God to dominate your heart, you need to be delivered
and when you are delivered, you begin to enjoy the Word of God.
Then, this can influence your character and your conduct.
You are disconnected in the name of Jesus!
Be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Let the will of God be done!
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, say after me, Take more of me, Lord, give me more of You -
more of Your obedience, faithfulness, kindness, purity, holiness.
Take more of me, oh Holy Spirit!
Take more of me - more of me, in Jesus' name!
Give me more of You, Lord.
Holy Spirit, give me more of you, Lord!
More of You, Lord!
More of Your holiness, purity, faithfulness, obedience, in Jesus' name!
I can hear you been saved.
Hallelujah.
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Worship Him! Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, your temple, your body is not its place (affliction, sickness).
You affliction in their temple - say, "Affliction in my body, I command you out!"
It can be in your blood - whatever, wherever it is, begin to flush them out!
In your bones, in your kidneys - I command healing in the name of Jesus!
In your liver!
Wherever that affliction, wherever that pain - open your lips and begin to command them out!
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name